<fomod>
  <Name>Dripping when aroused</Name>
  <Version>01-05-2016</Version>
  <Author>Ed86</Author>
  <Description>
  
Requires:
-SexLab Framework
-(Optional)SexLab Aroused (Redux), required for dripping
-(Optional)Schlongs of Skyrim, required for futa support
-(Optional)DDi/Zap, required for gag drooling support

  
Description:
When female becomes sufficiently aroused, her pussy will start leaking juices.(60s)
After having anal or vaginal intercourse, character will leak cum.(60s)
After having orgasm females will squirt.(10s)
Wearing Gag will cause drooling effect.(10s)
When player(character) is aroused enough, you will hear heartbeat, breathing and have a blurred vision.
All effects can be had at same time, effects work through clothes, affected npcs shown in mcm.
 
Your graphic settings, enb, etc can affect visibility of effects.
 
Mod runs checks on player character and actors within range every X seconds, If character aroused enough Mod applies hidden spell with 60 seconds duration.
 
 Cheat?: you can set Arousal_threshold to 0 and all females will be dripping(even if you have no SLA)

 You can increase sound volume in CK/TES Edit, see screen shot below
 
You can change breathing sound by replacing with your desired effects
data\sound\fx\dw\
there are some sound pack in thread

to enable male breathing you need to uncomment script DW_BreathSpellScr
		;elseif akActor.GetLeveledActorBase().GetSex() == 0		;male
		;	Sound1 = CORE.Breathing3
		;	Sound2 = CORE.Breathing4
also you need to supply sound files, instead of default ones(renamed female sound):
DW_Breathing_M_H_lp
DW_Breathing_M_L_lp
 
 
If you want to compile scripts, you need extracted sources of SL, SkyUi SDK, (for optional plug-ins respective sources: SLA, SOS, Zaz, DDi)
 
Meshes and textures taken from ZaZ Animation Pack/skyrim, meshes modified to work w/o equipping inventory item
Visuals and heartbeat taken from arousalvisuals-0.1 by idk who, which is lost during forum move. i've fixed scripts and annoying loop bug or was it feature?.

  </Description>
  <Website>http://www.loverslab.com/files/file/2300-dripping-when-aroused/</Website>
</fomod>